http://www.legendsofterris.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyLegends of Terris / Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://www.legendsofterris.com, operated by Online Games Company LtdWhat personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address,  browser user agent, referrer, and Site URL string, along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself to help spam detection via the Akismet anti-spam service.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website. Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Forum Profile InfoAll information in the profile is optional and expected to support your in-game character.  This information is viewable by other registered users.  We do not process this information.Game DetailsThe create character process collects email, name, your location and where you heard about the game.  Email and Name are used to help account recovery.  Heard About and Location is used to help us understand where people found out about the game.The IP address used when connecting to the game is recorded.AnalyticsHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Additional informationWe do not collect information from other sites or process or share your data beyond the requirements to operate the site.Data Protection OfficerAny requests or queries should be sent by email to sysop@onlinegamescompany.com
Recent Posts
October 2020
Newsletter
July 2020
June 2020
April 2020ArchivesOctober 2020August 2020June 2020April 2020March 2020July 2019November 2018July 2018April 2018June 2017May 2017January 2017July 2016February 2016January 2016August 2015June 2015November 2014September 2014July 2014May 2014April 2014March 2014January 2014December 2013September 2013August 2013June 2013CategoriesArchived UpdatesCurrent UpdateGame UpdatesNews
All content © 2020 Online Games Company.
Please read our privacy statement.Back to Top
